FELIPE GARCIA SUEZ

25/10/2000

Location:

Rosario, Santa Fe, Argentina

Phone:

+54 (0)341 366 - 9925

Email:

garciasuezfelipe@gmail.com

Summary

Full Stack Developer. I have experiences in projects using technologies like **Node** and **React-Redux** working as a freelancer and **Python** in my current job. I stand out for my ability to identify problems and my adaptation to the workflow in a team. Hardware knowledge with experience in the crypto world.

Experience

Solvo S.R.L March 2023 - Present

I work in a company in Rosario that is responsible for providing marketing and systems development services. I started as a Help-Desk for the first 3 months until I became familiar with the company system and then became a full-time developer.

My role in the company currently is to carry out development tasks using **Python** in back-end and **XML – CSS** in front-end, we work with an ERP system called Odoo in which we generate modules according to client requests.

The skills learned that stand out most from this job are:

- Programación orientada a objetos
- Management of accounting in systems
- Work based on tasks and objectives
- ERP's operation

Hardware technician – 06/2021 – 08/2022

CryptoRig is an enterprise formed between partners whose objective is the assembly and maintenance of crypto mining rigs. Working in this branch made me acquire knowledge based on the crypto world and the following qualities:

- Experience with computer hardware problems and operating system management.
- Work based on a time limit and specifications defined by the client, know how to treat it to keep it satisfied.
- Work as a team and make the company prosper and progress.

Freelancer - September 2022 - February 2023

I had the chance to sell projects as a freelancer through SCRUM methodology, most of them using **React-Redux** on the front-end and **NodeJS**, **Sequelize**, **Express** and **PostgreSQL** in back. These works were uploaded through a VPS using docker. Doing this job gave me the chance to understand the market of web programming and the commitment to the client to supply their order. I have some projects on my <u>personal portfolio</u>.

Education

Secondary: San Juan Bautista De La Salle 2013-2018

Bachelor of Economics and Administration.

soyHenry Full Stack Developer course +400 hours

Full-time course adapted to the labor market with teaching and practices in JavaScript, CSS, React, Redux, Node, Secuelize, Express and PostgreSQL.

Programming Technician - UTN Rosario 2023-2024

Currently studying the technical degree in the night shift, which aims to train students in the creation and maintenance of systems focused on companies. It lasts two years and some of the technologies on the schedule are Docker, React, Python, .NET, SQL and more.

Languages

English Intermidiate – C2 by EFSET certificate 77/100

I can understand reading and make simple conversations. I see myself as fully capable of navigating an English-speaking environment.